Hey, what's up everybody? I want to talk
to you about something that is a huge
topic. Been talking with my group about
it, but something I've been working
through, but something that for years I
have seen. What separates those who are
successful in their businesses online
from those that struggle is their
ability to take their perfectionism and
channel it in the right way. I'm a
recovering perfectionist, somebody who
always needs everything to be perfect.
But can I tell you this?
Perfectionism
is not the way to build a business
successfully.
Perfectionism feels like it's the right
way to do it. A spirit of excellence.
We're going to make sure that we do
everything right. We're going to make
sure that we get all the stuff right and
we get it done. But the truth is it is
one of the most detrimental things that
we can do. I want to challenge you on
that because again, as somebody who's a
recovering perfectionist, I understand
your desire to do the right things.
Nobody wants to lose money. Nobody wants
to hurt their clients. Nobody wants to
not deliver results. Of course, right?
We want to overd deliver all the time.
But perfectionism
is not the way to do that. In fact,
there's a process I learned the name of.
It's called imperfectionism. And it's
something that I find that that when I
operate in it, I get more done. As a
business owner, you need to learn to
operate in imperfectionism
where you start to embrace
things not going perfect. Meaning this,
it goes beyond just your actions, but
also your results. See, we desire to
have a control over things. We want
things to go well. I want to make sure
that I got my copyright, my ads, and all
of that before I launch a campaign so
that I don't lose any money and
everything goes perfect. And that right
there is a losing battle.
It's a setup for failure. It's actually
one of the number one things that will
keep you from success is having that
thinking in your mind. I want to make
sure that I got it all dialed in
so that I get the perfect result.
There's no such thing as a perfect
result. And what works so much better
than that is consistent imperfect
action. I've been preaching that,
preaching it literally for the longest
time.
But what I found is is that
in theory,
most people struggle with this. They're
looking to validate themselves through
perfection. They're looking to feel
certainty
and safety. They're looking to make sure
that things go well for them, that they
don't miss out on the goals that they
want. And of course, those are our
desires. The reason why people coach
with me, they're in my wealthy coach
academy program and I work with mentors,
trainers, coaches every single week to
dial in the nuances of what makes sure
that things click and they get results
for them. Our clients get results that
are in there.
But the number one thing that I tell
people is in fact you got to be willing
to put it out there and it not produce a
result and embrace the lessons you learn
just by doing the action just by taking
the imperfect action. That it's an
iterative process that there's a process
where part of your process
is is going to include a failed campaign
and that means that you did it the right
way.
part of your process means that you're
going to have some cost of tuition,
maybe a maybe a an offer that doesn't
convert how you want it to. And in fact,
the the the mission and the goal that we
have to not experience that
is the number one reason why you're not
experiencing the results that you want.
that when we can embrace
imperfection,
taking action,
good enough is good enough. Launch it
out there. We don't need it to be
perfect. I don't need this to be the
perfect video that's perfectly curated.
I don't need this to be the perfect
piece of content. I don't need my course
to be perfect before I put it out there.
And we get more to around imperfect
prolific
nature that it's the consistent prolific
nature. Being prolific means that you're
putting stuff out there consistently.
All right, I got a video out. I'm going
to get one out next week. I got a course
out. I'm going to get another one out
next week. I got an offer out. I'm going
to get another one out next week.
And that actually becomes your behavior.
I got new ads out. We're going to launch
new ones next week. We're not going to
sit on the laurels of this one thing
that I put together produces the result,
but rather it's the body of work.
It's the long-term consistent showing up
and being yourself and consistently
doing that. And then here's what I love
to do. Here's one of my favorite things.
A reductionist
viewpoint. What can I remove that's a
waste of time? I just did this in my
business.
I have a podcast. It's called the Grow
Your Life podcast. It has over like 350.
I think we're on like the 350s, some
somewhere around there. 325, 350,
something like that. And we stopped
counting.
And I decided, you know what?
My YouTube videos that I put here, we're
just going to put it up as the podcast.
We're gonna I'm not going to do a
dedicated podcast every week. I'm just
going to when I feel inspiration, I'm
going to record it. We're going to put
it on YouTube. my team is going to go
put it as a podcast. Reduced literally a
couple hours of my week right there
to keep things simple, to keep it
flowing, to keep it working.
Right now, it's about 512. I usually end
my day at 5. Kind of a crazy day here. I
had to leave and go do some stuff with
the family a little bit early. Told my
wife, let's order some dinner and I'll
I'll be done in about 10 minutes. No, 10
15 minutes after 5.
perfectly fine. But I came up with this
video. It's been something I've been
feeling in my heart that I want to share
with you for a while. And and and and
it's one of the number one things that
will literally produce the financial
returns you want.
It will produce.
And and by the way, I don't say that
flippantly that it's the number one
thing.
It is the number one thing. Everything
else kind of comes number two to this
when you get it. Embracing
the failures, the mistakes. You forgot
to record your video. You forgot to turn
your microphone on when you were
recording.
It's okay. It's part of the process.
It's part of that process. And then
here's one of the one of the biggest
things that you do that disappointment
that we feel. I learned I actually
learned this one. I studied it because I
wanted I wanted to get a tactic that
could help you guys. I went and I found
as many resources I could on this and I
learned this again from stock market
trading. It's been something I've been
I've been doing recently. Um had a great
month. Like I I I think I did like
30,000 in in profit from my trading
about a month ago and it was incredible.
This month's been a little bit lower.
That's kind of how it goes with trading
stocks. It's very interesting. like you
have a big month and you kind of like
it's not that I pulled back but it's
like okay what was the mojo that I had
then I lost it didn't lose it
technically but it's the mindset shift
and there's books that I read on this
topic and and one of the biggest things
is like okay like when you have a down
month
you want your emotions to be at a
baseline you don't want them to dip you
don't want to get flooded with those
negative emotions you want the the the
darkest negative moment moments
to actually be your baseline of
positivity.
And then your highs, you don't want them
to be so high that you got to come down
with them that you're so euphoric.
Finding a balance of the highs and lows
emotionally when we accomplish things,
when we have we hit a great month, when
we have a great
a great year in our business, right?
My biggest month prior to that, I did
like $8,000 in the stock market. Uh, and
then I I some of y'all have heard the
story. I lost like 12,000 in 15 minutes.
Uh, the the next the next week uh made
it back quadruple back because I know
how to do that. This month, you know,
been kind of break even. Um, made some,
lost some, made some, lost some. Okay,
what's going on? What am I What am I not
doing that I was doing when I hit that
$30,000 month? I can literally I start
to pinpoint it. I start to notice the
emotions inside of me. I really focus on
those, regulating them, keeping them
solid. Not that I'm numbed out, not that
I'm not emotional. This is a huge part
of it. You you you have emotion, but you
reframe them. And you reframe what your
baseline is. And so you get to where
okay, the hardest, darkest thing that
happens,
that's kind of your baseline. and then
everything else can flow from there
rather than I have this low like oh
because what I wanted because I know
that like losing having a losing trade
is going to be part of the process this
week has been crazy in the market had a
losing trade because the president
tweeted a couple times at China
okay
but I didn't lose more because of that
and I'm thankful that I actually
protected my assets because of that some
people lost their whole portfolios in
the last week I did Not. I can still
trade. Can still make that money back.
Make it back in a week.
Probably will. I'm declaring it right
now. Probably will. Totally.
But those that that lesson that I
learned in that, I bring it to business.
And I actually wish I knew it in
business
years ago. In my business, I can see the
value of it. It doesn't just apply to
stock trading. It applies in my
relationship with my family. It applies
in how I show up with my clients.
You know, I used to get really like when
I had a client that was disappointed or
was negative or they felt uh upset with
me, it would it would just ruin me
inside. Now, it's like I'm like, "Okay,
let's just let's take a look at what's
going on here." And how do I show up as
a leader? the leader that I'm called to
be, the leader that I'm meant to be,
to be a strong, powerful leader that
doesn't lead from a place of dictation,
but rather with love and kindness
and can help guide people in that. How
do I show up with my family when I'm
having a tough day?
All these things are interconnected.
And I I truly believe how you do one
thing is how you do everything. how I
show up in my emotions. Sure, I might
have one area of my life where I'm
really solid in it and others where I
struggle, but the but the the big
picture of how I live my life outside of
my business, outside of trading,
in my relationships is also how I show
up and everything else. And so if if
there's a if there's a moment where I'm
getting flustered
because these things happen,
I'm going to say, "Okay, I'm pro I'm
getting flustered in other areas of my
life. I notice this." And so I don't
need to be perfect with my family. I
don't need to be perfect with my spouse.
By the way, my wife does not want me to
be. She knows that if I'm trying and
striving to be that way, she says, "I
show up kind of like an an a-hole in our
family a little bit." She's like, "Dude,
you're trying too hard to be perfect
and you're running all over everybody
and and being a jerk to everybody."
And when I just kind of let go and have
fun and let loose and do a little dance
a little bit, even with the kids or
something like that, right? I do a
little dance in my business. Doing a
little dance here on this video.
Everything flows from that so much
better. The sales copy comes together. I
can literally shrink the amount of time
that it takes me to accomplish things
when I flow from that place.
Stuff that would have taken me hours to
do, I could get done in 30 minutes.
Literally did that today.
It's powerful. Powerful to see that. I
want to encourage you. You can
accomplish anything that you want to. I
believe in you.
But there are things inside of you,
shifts that you have to make. Behaviors,
things that you've held on to for your
whole life,
things that that you've always done, how
you've always shown up as success
strategies that you're going to have to
fix or you're not going to be
successful. And if you don't change
them, success is going to escape you.
You literally will not be capable of
success operating in certain habits and
behaviors and ways of doing things when
you do them in your business. And it
takes growth. This is the personal
growth journey that can change your
life.
It's changed mine. It's changed it's
changed my family. It's changed a lot of
these lessons my mother has taught me,
has imparted to me. I've seen as
her just the the multi-millionaire
powerful woman that she is.
She's a mentor to me every single day.
And but I've seen it firsthand. And I
and gosh, I thought the cocky person I
was, I thought I knew everything about
business years ago when I was working
with her. And now I'm like, I don't know
anything, but I'm learning more and more
and I can accomplish more and do
anything I want to. Listen,
if you're a coach, if you're a mentor,
I'd love to work with you inside my
Wealthy Coach Academy program. I'd love
to see you in there. Get into a
community of people that are making it
happen.
I'd love to work with you in there and
get those results for you as well. We'll
see you soon. Real soon. Have a good
one. Subscribe to the channel. Love you.
Bye.